# KEIICHI KATSUNO

FULL-STACK WEB DEVELOPER



## PERSONAL SKILLS

- Emotional Awareness
- Problem Solving
- Individual Collaboration
- Relationship Development
- Research & Market Expansion

## TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Ruby on Rails (Ruby)
- Javascript (ES6)
- HTML5 / CSS / Bootstrap
- SQLite / PostgreSQL
- GitHub

### LANGUAGES

- Japanese (Native)
- English (Professional)
- Spanish (Elementary)

# INTERESTS

- Weight Training
- American Football
- Specialty Coffee
- Non-Fiction (e.g. Anthropology / History / Business etc)

# CONTACT

20 Newton Street Kensington, Victoria 3031 045 255 3653 keichi031605@gmail.com

## **PROFILE**

Ruby on Rails Developer. Deep interest in SaaS and passionate about business improvement that has a real influence on people's life.

For the past 6 years, I've engaged in Marketing and Relationship Development in Japan, and Production Management in The UK and Colombia. I've been focusing on solving the problems and meeting the needs of stakeholders as well as team members. I've gained many achievements and developed the ability to collaborate individually to work in a team and build firm relationships with diverse people.

I place a high value on **Respect to People** and **Learning Independently** in my life.

## **EXPERIENCE**

#### **QUALITY ASSURANCE SPECIALIST**

InverCafé Ltda., Chinchiná, Colombia | Sep 2019 - Dec 2019 (Internship)

- Deep Industrial Knowledge
- Market Research & Analysis
- Conversational Spanish

#### PRODUCTION MANAGER

The Roasting Shed Co., London, The UK | July 2018 - Sep 2019 (Full-time)

- Production Analysis & Development
- Market Research & Analysis
- Business English Proficiency

#### **RELATIONSHIP MANAGER**

Yuasa Trading Co., Osaka & Fukuoka, Japan | Apr 2013 - July 2017 (Full-time)

- Relationship Development
- Project Management
- Sales & Marketing
- Negotiation

## **EDUCATION**

#### **BACHELOR OF BUSINESS ADMINISTRATION. SPORTS MANAGEMENT**

Kinki University, Osaka, Japan | Apr 2009 - Mar 2013

Outside of study, I engaged in American Football club where I learned:

- Organisational Theory
- Team Management
- Logical & Critical Thinking for organisational success.

## **PROJECT**

## "WHATSPOT" (SPOT SHARING SERVICE)

- The mobile app that you can share any places or recommendations with your friends so that you get more trustable information for your weekend!

Please find all my projects from my portfolio page.

- My Portfolio: https://keiichi031605.github.io/keiichi-portfolio/